# **COSTA ANTON**

### Video Game Programmer

- @ costa.anton@hotmail.com
   https://antoncosta.github.io/

## INTRODUCTION

#### Hello.

I'm Costa, a video game programmer from Romania. I am an open-minded, hard-working, individual who consistently strives to attain new knowledge and new experiences. Curiosity has always pushed me forward to try new things and I, without fail, have the perseverance to finish what I start. I consider myself to be a fast learner, or, at the very least, persevering enough to learn as quickly as possible. Apart from the education at universities in Romania I have done one semester in Krakow in Poland and 1 year of study in the Netherlands, both part of an ERASMUS scholarship. I have quickly adapted to both countries and have learned a lot from these experiences.

# **EXPERIENCE**

# European Economic Area(EEA) Placement Grant University of Iceland

Reykjavík, Iceland

 A two-month mobility in Iceland to work at the university on a research project. I developed a Virtual Reality application in the Unity game engine to help people that suffer from Acrophobia (fear of heights).

## Full time Programmer/Localisation Engineer Pragmatic Play

🛗 Jan 2019 - Jun 2019

Bucharest, Romania

A Unity game engine developer for slots games. My task was
to create Unity editor extensions, or to continue existing
extensions, to help streamline the game production. I was also
part of the localisations team and we were responsible for the
maintenance of the application in the case that problems
might appear in certain languages.

#### Intern

## **Property Shark**

mar 2018 - Sep 2018

♥ Cluj-Napoca, Cluj, Romania

 A six-month period of internship. One half of it working with Visual Basic to do User Acceptance Tests. The second half was with C# creating and modifying ASP.NET applications. Both of them related the "PropertyShark - Real Estate Search and Property Information " website

### Summer Intern

### **FIDA Solutions**

🛗 Jul 2017 - Aug 2017

Paia Mare, Maramures, Romania

 Summer internship, worked 6 weeks with JavaScript, HTML and CSS developing maps for different sectors of Romania, mostly focusing on urban areas and how to manage new buildings and space in general.

## **SKILLS**

Unity
C#
Unreal
C, C++
Java
Angular2
Python
JavaScript
Spring
Blender
Maya

## **INTERESTS**

#### **Technical**

- Video Game Programming and Design
- Shaders & Computer Graphics
- Animation
- Sound Design

#### **Hobbies**

- Playing video games.
- Writing fantasy stories.
- Travelling.
- Listening to audio books.
- Juggling and Magic.

# **LANGUAGES**

English Romanian French Polish



# **STRENGTHS**

Hard-working Fast learner Curious
Imaginative Adaptable

Game Engines

Video Game Design & Development

Mobile Applications

# **EDUCATION**

# Master's Degree, Graphics, Multimedia and Virtual Reality

## **University Politehnica of Bucharest**

**2018 - 2020** 

**9** Bucharest, Romania

The Master focused on Computer Graphics mostly, OpenGL, C++ and video game engines, video game design and development, as well as a bit of marketing advice. Along with game engine, there was also an emphasis on Virtual Reality, as most university projects related to virtual reality were done by the computer graphics department.

## Master's Degree, Computer Graphics

## **University of Groningen**

**2019 - 2020** 

**Q** Groningen, Netherlands

Part of an ERASMUS+ study exchange. I have continued the master's that I have started in Bucharest on Computer Graphics, Multimedia and Virtual Reality.

Bachelor's Degree, Computer Science Babes-Bolyai University

**2015 - 2018** 

♥ Cluj-Napoca, Romania

Web development focused, emphasis on OOP, it's principles and mobile applications as well as website development for mobile environments.

\_\_\_\_\_

# Bachelor's Degree, Computer Science AGH University of Science and Technology

**2017 - 2017** 

♥ Kraków, Poland

Exchange student for one semester with ERASMUS+. I mainly did courses in the field of Computer Science which were equivalent with what I would have done back home, one exception being a Polish Language course which was for exchange students.

High School, Mathematics and Informatics National College "Gheorghe Sincai"

**#** 2011 - 2015

Paia Mare, Romania

# **REFERENCES**

Prof. Dr. Ing. Alin Moldoveanu @ alin.moldoveanu@cs.pub.ro

**Dr. Jiří Kosinka @** j.kosinka@rug.nl